autobarn.com.au 2015-04-02

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Metcash Limited ACN 112 073 480, including Automotive Brands Group Pty Ltd, their related bodies corporate and  business pillars (collectively, “ **Metcash** ”, “we”, “our” or “us”) is committed to the protection of personal privacy within the scope of applicable law. This Privacy Policy covers Metcash's treatment of personal information that we collect, use and disclose.

Metcash may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version will be located on the Metcash websites, and is also available by contacting our Privacy Officer by email or at the address detailed below.

By using any of the Metcash websites, or by providing any personal information to Metcash, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy.

## Types of personal information collected

The types of personal information collected and held by Metcash will vary depending on your dealings with us. This information may include any or all of the following:

  * name, address(es), telephone number(s) and other contact details; 
  * associated company name(s), position, occupation and other business details;
  * electronic address(es);
  * bank account details;
  * credit card details; and
  * transaction details relating to your use of our products, services or benefits.

We will also collect your date of birth and driver’s licence number where required (for example, to comply with age restrictions or in order to verify your identity when applying for credit terms, etc).

From time to time, you may provide us, and we may collect from you, personal information of a third party (for example, for delivery purposes). Where you provide the personal information of a third party, it is your responsibility to ensure that those persons are aware of this Privacy Policy, understand it and agree to accept it.

Metcash will not collect sensitive information from you or any third party.

You do not have to provide us with any personal information, however if you do not do so we may not be able to complete a transaction you have entered into, finalise payment of a product or service you have ordered, make delivery of a product you have ordered, grant credit terms, validate your entry in a promotion, or otherwise provide you with the products, services or benefits you have requested.

## How Metcash collects personal information

Generally, Metcash collects personal information directly from you, such as:

  * when you personally submit information through a Metcash website;
  * in person (such as in store);
  * when you apply for credit terms;
  * when you enter into a promotion conducted by us or a third party;
  * when you complete a survey;
  * in the course of us providing you with a requested product, service or benefit; or
  * when you have other dealings with us.

Metcash will collect personal information through:

  * Metcash Limited, its related bodies corporate and its business pillars;
  * our business partners who may partner with Metcash for promotional activities; and
  * third parties who supply services to Metcash.

## Why Metcash collects, uses and discloses personal information

Metcash will use the personal information it collects for the purpose disclosed at the time of collection, or otherwise as set out in this Privacy Policy. Metcash will not use your personal information for any other purpose without first seeking your consent, or where authorised or required by law.

Metcash will collect personal information for the following purposes:

  * to establish and maintain your relationship with us, including in some cases disclosing your name and address (as required by law, such as to government authorities and agencies) and providing you with information necessary to allow you to remain in contact with Metcash;
  * to provide the products or services you have requested from us and keep a record of them; to provide credit to you, which may include disclosures to credit reporting agencies or bodies;
  * to answer any inquiry you make;
  * to register you for events or promotions; or
  * to assist us to make our services and products more valuable or useful to you.

Metcash may also disclose your personal information to third parties who work with us in our business to provide, promote or improve the products or services you have requested or are interested in, such as:

  * manufacturers and suppliers; couriers and delivery contractors;
  * marketing consultants and promotions companies; website hosts; and
  * consultants and professional advisers.

Metcash will also use and disclose your personal information to send direct marketing to you from:

  * Metcash Limited, its related bodies corporate and its business pillars; and
  * third parties who provide services to us;

The direct marketing may relate to:

  * our products and services;
  * the products and services of other parties;
  * promotions run by us or other parties; or
  * to keep you informed of new developments we believe may be of interest to you.

You may opt-out of receiving this direct marketing from Metcash or third parties through the unsubscribe function that will be made available to you with each direct marketing communication.

## How Metcash stores and protects personal information

Metcash stores personal information in a combination of computer storage facilities, paper-based files and other records. In so doing, we have taken numerous steps to protect your personal information from misuse, interference and loss, and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

Additionally Metcash takes reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information when we no longer need it.

The internet is not a secure method of transmitting information. Accordingly, other than where Metcash uses secure socket layer technology (SSL) to ensure information (such as credit card information) is securely transmitted and processed, Metcash cannot and does not accept responsibility for the security of information you send to or receive from us over the internet, or for any unauthorised access or use of that information.

## Does Metcash send personal information overseas?

Metcash is likely to disclose some of your personal information, for the purposes described above, to organisations in other countries, including the United States of America.

Some of these countries may not have the same or substantially similar privacy laws as those set out in this privacy policy and the Australian Privacy Principles.  We may not require organisations to which we disclose personal information in those countries to comply with similar privacy laws, and accordingly your personal information may not receive the same protections that it would in Australia.  By providing your personal information to us, you consent to our disclosure of your personal information to organisations in those countries even though it may not receive the same protections that it would in Australia.

## How you can access your personal information

Metcash will take reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up to date. If your personal details change, such as your address or phone number, please contact our Privacy Officer by email or at the address detailed below.

At your request, Metcash will provide you with a copy of any personal information which we hold about you, unless an exception under the _Privacy Act 1988_ applies. We may charge a fee for retrieving this information, in which case we will inform you of the fee and obtain your agreement to that fee before providing the information.

We will promptly acknowledge and investigate any complaint about the way we manage personal information.

## Cookies

The Metcash websites use cookies to track user traffic patterns and to better serve you when you revisit a website. A cookie is a small data file that a website may write to your hard drive when you visit it. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user ID which the website uses to track the pages you have visited. You can refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, full functionality for the Metcash websites requires the use of cookies.

Information is also generated whenever a page is accessed on a Metcash website that records information such as the time, date and specific page. We collect such information for statistical and maintenance purposes that enables us to continually evaluate our website performance.

## How to contact Metcash or make a complaint

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, if you wish to update information we hold about you or if you wish to make a complaint about our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information under this Privacy Policy, please contact:

## The Privacy Officer

Metcash Limited 50 Waterloo Road

Macquarie Park NSW 2113 Fax: (02) 9741 3027

E-mail: [privacy@metcash.com](mailto:privacy@metcash.com)

Metcash will take reasonable steps to remedy any issues resulting from our failure to comply with our privacy obligations.

Last updated January 2014
